export const pythonOperatorsConditionalsExercise = {
  title: 'Python Operators & Conditionals â€“ Exercise',
  questions: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'Which operator is used for exponentiation?',
      options: ['^', '**', '%', '//'],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'Which operator gives remainder?',
      options: ['/', '//', '%', '*'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'Which operator checks equality?',
      options: ['=', '==', '!=', '<'],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: 'Result of (10 > 5) is?',
      options: ['True', 'False', '10', '5'],
      correctIndex: 0,
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: 'Which logical operator returns true if both conditions are true?',
      options: ['or', 'not', 'and', 'if'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: 'Which keyword starts a condition?',
      options: ['for', 'while', 'if', 'def'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: 'Which operator reverses a condition?',
      options: ['and', 'or', 'not', '!='],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: 'Which operator is used for floor division?',
      options: ['/', '//', '%', '**'],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: 'Conditional statements depend on?',
      options: ['Loops', 'Operators', 'Functions', 'Input'],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: 'Which statement runs when condition is false?',
      options: ['if', 'elif', 'else', 'pass'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
  ],
}